Donald Rockmore

Union City, Georgia 30291

Phone: (770)990-8406 | Email: Donaldrockmore@yahoo.com LinkedIn: Donald Rockmore | GitHub: https://github.com/DRockmore89 | Portfolio: Write out Link

Objective

To obtain an active position, where I can exhibit my technical, leadership, and collaborative skills, while contributing to the advancement and growth of the company. Utilize exceptional IT, problem solving, and communication skills.

Education

February 2021- Present Georgia Tech. Atlanta. GA

Certification: Georgia Tech Full Stack Web Development

Paine College, Augusta, GA August 2009- December 2012

Degree: Bachelor of Business Administration

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in proactive customer-oriented service and a life-long dedication to learning. Effective at combining computer literacy, critical thinking, and problem-solving skills to develop user-friendly, customizable applications. Known among staff, peers, and coworkers for attention to detail, time management, collaboration skills, and strong desire to fully grasp concepts, despite the various complexities of the task.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & React

Projects

| Link to Deployed My Mental Project [https://mikebird2414.github.io/Well-Being/]

- Working on this project was a great experience. Bouncing idea was the best part for me, that is when your creative side explores.
- My core responsibilities in the project were the Front-End and Back End.
- Tools- Javascript, Advanced HTML, CSS
- Dependencies: express, mysq12l, sequelize, express-handlebars

Experience

United States Postal Service - Mail Technician 848 Oglethorpe Ave, Atlanta, GA 30310

September 2018 - Present

- Create and maintain interpersonal relationships
- Cater services to the individual needs of customers
- Safely operate company vehicles
- Responsibly utilize the company card for business purchases
- Safeguard important personal documents
- Utilize critical thinking skills and problem/solution skills while responding to customer complaints

Clayton County Public Schools - Maintenance

July 2015 - September 2018

7728 Mt. Zion Blvd, Jonesboro, GA 30236

- Installed and maintain school computer and public announcement systems
- Assisted office staff with computer application questions
- Conducted inspections of malfunctioning equipment and software
- Repaired malfunctioning office printers and RISO copier
- Provided ongoing support to users regarding system network and internet connectivity
- Developed and improved strong communication and technical skills
- Maintained a clean environment conducive to learning
- Assessed and reported the need for work repairs

7950 Spence Road, Fairburn, GA 30213

- Accurately recorded information on company database to minimize stock waste
- Efficiently moved stock in and out of warehouse
- Consistently followed company policies and objectives
- Answered inquiries from transport managers
- Packaged and labeled stock before shipped out of warehouse
- Implemented procedures of storage of hazardous material
- Met and greeted visitors

Malcolm Cunningham Ford - Sales and Leasing Consultant

January 2012 - September 2013

4334 Snapfinger Woods Drive, Decatur GA

- Represented the company at trade exhibitions, events, and demonstrations
- Promoted upgrades, such as: financing, insurance products, and paint protection
- Possessed a knowledge of lot inventory
- Reported to the vehicle sales manager on activities, reviews, and analysis
- Contacted, met, discussed, and followed up with prospective buyers
- Negotiated the terms of sales agreements, completed sales contracts, and closed sales
- Arranged appointments via internet leads
- Prepared car purchase packages
- Delivered vehicles to customers
- Collaborated with the showroom body shop to ensure that vehicle repairs were carried out quickly and efficiently

Key Accomplishments:

- Talk about all of your new positions at work. Like that thing at the post office that lock is....
- If applicable, bullet-point 2-4 key value-adds or recognitions, i.e., awards, nominations, special assignments, leadership, praise, etc.